<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitTrack</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome back</string>
    <string name="all_workouts_are_personalized_for_you">All workouts are personalized for you</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="aboutus">\t\t\FitTrack is a versatile fitness app designed to help you achieve your health goals, whether you prefer exercising at home or joining our exclusive offline gym membership program. Our app combines convenience with expert guidance, providing personalized workout plans, attendance tracking, and a comprehensive diet guide to support your fitness journey. \n\n\t\t\tMission Our mission is to make fitness accessible and achievable for everyone, no matter where they are. We aim to empower individuals with the tools, guidance, and motivation to take charge of their health and fitness, blending technology with a personal touch. \n\n\t\t\tVision We envision a world where fitness is part of everyday life, not an extra task. Through FitTrack, we strive to create a seamless fitness experience that combines the best of home workouts and offline gym programs, helping individuals live healthier, more active lives.</string>
    <string name="services">Home Workouts : Access expertly designed workout routines that can be done at home, customized to your fitness level and goals. \n\nOffline Gym Membership : For those looking for in-person training, our offline membership program allows users to sign up, pay their fees, and receive a digital membership card. This card can be scanned by our representatives to mark attendance and keep your account updated. \n\nAttendance Tracking : Keep track of your gym attendance with our easy-to-use membership card, ensuring that your workouts are logged automatically. \n\nDiet Guide : GymnesticApp offers a comprehensive diet guide with detailed food information and personalized meal suggestions, ensuring that your nutrition aligns with your fitness goals. \n\nProgress Tracking : Monitor your progress with in-app analytics, set goals, and stay motivated with regular updates on your fitness achievements.</string>
    <string name="corevalues">Simplicity : Making fitness easy and accessible for everyone. \n\nFlexibility : Catering to both home-based workouts and gym enthusiasts. \n\nAccountability : Helping users stay consistent with automatic attendance tracking and progress monitoring. \n\nSupport : Providing personalized guidance and nutritional insights to keep you on track.</string>
    <string name="why_fittrack">\t\t\tAt FitTrack, we believe fitness should be simple, effective, and flexible. Whether you\'re working out at home or at the gym, our app offers the best of both worlds, combining digital convenience with real-world support. With FitTrack, you have everything you need in one place to stay on track with your fitness goals.</string>
</resources>